const quizData = [
  
    {
      "question": "What fraction of a day is 8 hours?",
      "options": ["1/6","2/3","1/3","2/5"],
      "answer": "1/3",
      "difficulty": "easy",
    },
    {
      "question": "If there are 8 slices in a pizza, how many slices is 1/4th of the pizza?",
      "options": ["4","2","3","5"],
      "answer": "2",
      "difficulty": "easy",
    },
    {
      "question": "The correct comparison symbol for the equation: 2005/2005 __ 1 is?",
      "options": [">","<","=","none"],
      "answer": "=",
      "difficulty": "medium",
    },
    {
      "question": "The correct comparison symbol for the equation: 1/4 ___ 9/36 is?",
      "options": ["<","=",">","none"],
      "answer": "=",
      "difficulty": "medium",
    },
    {
      "question": "What fraction of an hour is 15 minutes?",
      "options": ["1/4","2/3","1/3","2/5"],
      "answer": "1/4",
      "difficulty": "easy",
    },
    {
      "question": "______ is the equivalent fraction of 2/5?",
      "options": ["2/7","4/15","8/10","16/40"],
      "answer": "16/40",
      "difficulty": "hard",
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the equivalent fraction of 6/15 with a denominator of 5?",
      "options": ["3/9","5/6","4/5","2/5"],
      "answer": "2/5",
      "difficulty": "hard",
    },
    {
      "question": "Reduce the fraction 90/120 to its simplest form?",
      "options": ["2/3","4/5","5/9","3/4"],
      "answer": "3/4",
      "difficulty": "medium",
    },
    {
      "question": "1/8 + 3/8 = ___?",
      "options": ["2/8","9/4","4/8","4/16"],
      "answer": "4/8",
      "difficulty": "easy",
    },
    {
      "question": "7/17 + 9/17 = ___?",
      "options": ["15/34","16/34","16/17","15/17"],
      "answer": "16/17",
      "difficulty": "medium",
    }

];

export default quizData;


